Raymond Spilman Papers
Raymond Spilman Papers
- Business files (Part I)
  - ISCC
    - Board of Directors Meetings Reports, 1970-1971 (Box 15)
    - Medallion Design, 1970-1972 (Box 15)
    - Miscellaneous, 1960-1973; 3 folders (Box 15)
    - Miscellaneous, 1960-1973; 2 folders (Box 16)
    - [Miscellaneous], 1970-1974 (Box 42)
    - Problem 20, 1961 (Box 16)
  - ITEK, 1959-1964 (Box 16)
  - Itineraries, 1960-1970; 3 folders (Box 16)
  - ITT (Box 16)
  - Jervis Corporation, 1963 (Box 16)
  - Job Applications, 1954-1962; 3 folders (Box 16)
  - Johns-Mansville Corporation
    - Miscellaneous, 1953-1964; 2 folders (Box 16)
    - Proposals, 1961-1962 (Box 16)
  - Jones and Lamson Machine Company, 1964-1969; 2 folders (Box 16)
  - Mr. Robert L. Jordan, 1964-1965 (Box 16)
  - Keltec, 1966; 2 folders (Box 16)
  - Kent State University, 1967 (Box 16)
  - Kitchen Utensil Catalogues, 1968 (Box 16)
  - Knobs/Controls, 1959 (Box 16)
  - William C. Knox, 1964 (Box 16)
  - Kolb Book, 1965-1966 (Box 16)
  - Aarre K. Lahti, 1964-1968 (Box 16)
  - Lawn Furniture Strapping, 1971 (Box 16)
  - Lear-Siegler, 1974 (Box 16)
  - Licensing Committee, 1965-1968 (Box 16)
  - Lilliston Implement Company
    - Billing, 1959-1962 (Box 16)
    - Consultation Correspondence, 1959-1960 (Box 16)
    - Consultation Reports, 1959-1962 (Box 16)
    - General, 1957-1960 (Box 16)
    - General correspondence, 1961 (Box 16)
    - General correspondence, 1962-1966 (Box 17)
    - Logos and Stationery (Box 17)
    - Miscellaneous, 1964 (Box 17)
    - Peanut Combine, 1961; 1963; 2 folders (Box 17)
    - Reprints (Box 17)
  - Lima Electric Motor Company, Inc., 1960 (Box 17)
  - Logos (Box 17)
  - Machine Tools, 1961 (Box 17)
  - Machlett Laboratories, Inc., 1973 (Box 17)
  - Mack Trucks, Inc.
    - Billing File, 1963 (Box 17)
    - Correspondence, 1959-1963 (Box 17)
    - Extra Copies, 1962-1963 (Box 17)
    - Proposal and Contract File, 1963 (Box 17)
  - Magazine Clippings (Box 17)
  - Magazines, 1961-1968 (Box 17)
  - Magnesium Marketing Study, 1966 (Box 17)
  - Mallinckrodt Chemical Works, 1960-1961 (Box 17)
  - Bob Malone, 1965 (Box 17)
  - Marathon Oil Company, 1964 (Box 17)
  - Marketing Articles, 1958 (Box 17)
  - Martin Company, 1961-1963 (Box 17)
  - Maxwell House
    - MH-2, -3, -4 and -5, 1965-1966 (Box 17)
    - MH-4, 1965-1966 (Box 17)
    - Container Research, 1966 (Box 17)
    - Containers, 1965 (Box 17)
    - Correspondence, 1965 (Box 17)
    - General Foods Notes, 1960-1961 (Box 17)
    - Industrial Drawings, 1965 (Box 17)
    - Miscellaneous, 1963-1966 (Box 17)
    - Packaging Program, 1965 (Box 17)
    - Proposals, 1961-1962 (Box 17)
  - Melnor Industries, Inc., 1963 (Box 17)
  - Memo to Management (Box 17)
  - Metal Samples
    - John L. Armitage Company (Box 17)
    - Art Metal (Box 17)
    - Duralac Chemical Company (Box 17)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 17)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 18)
    - Photo-Lettering, Inc. (Box 18)
    - [Unidentified] (Box 42)
  - Miscellaneous, 1952-1976; 18 folders (Box 18)
  - Miscellaneous, 1952-1976; 17 folders (Box 19)
  - Miscellaneous, 1952-1976; 10 folders (Box 20)
  - Miscellaneous, 1956-1974; 2 folders (Box 42)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 90)
  - Miscellaneous Copies of Correspondence, 1970 (Box 20)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1963-1970 (Box 20)
  - Miscellaneous Industrial Drawings, 1957-1961; 2 folders (Box 20)
  - Miscellaneous Sketches, 1964-1965 (Box 20)
  - MIT Student Publication (Box 20)
  - Models, See Product models and samples below, at end of Business files series.
  - Monroe
    - General Correspondence, 1960-1962 (Box 20)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 20)
  - Motorola, Inc., 1969 (Box 20)
  - Moyer-Stiner-Spilman, 1953 (Box 20)
  - Moynahan Bronze Company, 1961 (Box 20)
  - Peter Muller-Munk, 1964-1965 (Box 20)
  - Museum of Contemporary Crafts, 1972 (Box 20)
  - Mutual Products, 1969 (Box 20)
  - MOMA, 1958-1964 (Box 20)
  - National Bureau of Standards Brochure, 1962 (Box 20)
  - Nautilus Industries, 1962 (Box 20)
  - NCR (The National Cash Register Company), 1962 (Box 20)
  - Negatives from Trade Fairs (Box 20)
  - New Line Furniture Proposal, 1964 (Box 20)
  - Norden
    - Aerolog, 1963-1964 (Box 20)
    - Billing Folder, 1963-1964 (Box 20)
    - Contract, 1964 (Box 20)
    - Miscellaneous, 1963; 1966; 2 folders (Box 20)
    - Proposal, 1963-1964 (Box 21)
  - North Carolina State College School of Design Speech, 1959-1960 (Box 21)
  - Northern Illinois University, 1969 (Box 21)
  - Office Outfitting Tasks (Box 21)
  - Office Plan, 1971 (Box 42)
  - Old Applications (Box 21)
  - Olin, 1965-1975 (Box 21)
  - Optomechanisms, 1965-1966 (Box 21)
  - Orbit International, 1967 (Box 21)
  - ORB-1, 1967 (Box 21)
  - Ortho Pharmaceutical Corporation, 1963 (Box 21)
  - Pace
    - Exercycle, 1972 (Box 21)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 21)
  - Package Content Lists, 1963-1965 (Box 21)
  - Package Content Lists, 1964-1969 (Box 42)
  - Packaging Review and Project Estimate, 1964 (Box 21)
  - Paint Talk, 1953 (Box 21)
  - Palco
    - Miscellaneous (Box 21)
    - WPA, 1971 (Box 21)
  - Pan American Design, 1967 (Box 21)
  - Bruce Payne and Associates
    - Information, 1960-1962 (Box 21)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 21)
  - PB Enterprises/Proposals, 1970-1971 (Box 21)
  - PBE-1, 1970-1971 (Box 21)
  - PC-11, 1965 (Box 21)
  - PC-12, Inquiries, 1965 (Box 21)
  - Peabody College Talk, 1960-1961 (Box 21)
  - Pearce-Simpson, Inc., 1962 (Box 21)
  - Peerless Manufacturing Division, 1960-1961 (Box 21)
  - Pending Client Proposals, 1964 (Box 21)
  - Persons-Majestic Manufacturing Co., 1954-1960 (Box 21)
  - PG Invoices, 1972 (Box 21)
  - Philadelphia Museum School Speech, 1958 (Box 21)
  - Philadelphia Museum Seminar Talk, 1960 (Box 21)
  - Philbrook Water Purifier, 1971 (Box 21)
  - Philosophy-Statements (Box 21)
  - Photographs, 6 folders (Box 21)
  - Photostat Corporation
    - [General], 1959 (Box 21)
    - [General], 1959-1962 (Box 22)
    - [General] (Box 90)
  - Picker X-Ray, 1967-1970 (Box 22)
  - Pickering and Company, Inc.
    - Billing, 1959-1961 (Box 22)
    - Design Program and Proposal, 1964 (Box 22)
    - General Correspondence, 1963 (Box 22)
    - General File, 1958; 2 folders (Box 22)
    - Miscellaneous, 1958-1959; 1971; 3 folders (Box 22)
    - PC-1, 1954; 1955 (Box 22)
    - PC-2, -3, and -4, 1957 (Box 22)
    - PC-5, 1957-1958 (Box 22)
    - PC-6 (Box 22)
  - Planning, 1958-1960 (Box 22)
  - Plastic Samples (Box 22)
  - Portion Control Company of America, 1964 (Box 22)
  - Poznan International Fair, 1962; 1963; 4 folders (Box 22)
  - Pratt Institute, 1963 (Box 22)
  - Primus-Sievert, Inc. (Box 22)
  - Prince Gardner, Inc., 1960-1961 (Box 22)
  - Product Engineering, 1964-1965 (Box 22)
  - Product models and samples, See Product models and samples below, at end of Business files series.
  - Professional Evaluation Committee Reports, 1962 (Box 22)
  - Promotion Letters, 1958-1960 (Box 22)
  - Published Material
    - Bicycle Journal, 1964; 2 issues (Box 22)
  - Radiation, Inc.
    - General Correspondence, 1957-1964; 2 folders (Box 22)
    - Lectures
      - #1 (Box 22)
      - #2, 1960 (Box 22)
    - Miscellaneous, 1958; 1964; 2 folders (Box 22)
    - Photographs (Box 22)
    - Photographs, 3 folders (Box 23)
    - Presentations and Proposals, 1958-1959 (Box 23)
    - Proposals Pending, 1959-1960 (Box 23)
  - Radio Broadcast Questions and Answers (Box 23)
  - Randall
    - 1967-1969, 2 folders (Box 23)
    - RA-1, 1963-1969; 2 folders (Box 23)
    - RA-2, 1968 (Box 23)
  - Raytheon Company
    - 1962-1964 (Box 23)
    - Report on Industrial Design, 1962 (Box 23)
  - RCA (Box 23)
  - Reel to Reel Tapes
    - ASID, Boston (Box 23)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 23)
    - Wearever
      - Master I (Box 23)
      - Master II (Box 23)
      - Master III (Box 23)
  - Reliance Manufacturing Company
    - Correspondence and Billing, 1960 (Box 23)
    - Package Story, 1960 (Box 23)
    - Packaging, 1960 (Box 23)
    - Proposal and Correspondence, 1958-1966 (Box 23)
  - Reprints, 1965 (Box 23)
  - Revere Copper and Brass Inc., 1969; miscellaneous; 2 folders (Box 23)
  - Reynolds Proposal, 1965 (Box 23)
  - Rhode Island School of Design
    - Bulletins, 1961-1963 (Box 23)
    - Correspondence, 1969-1970 (Box 23)
  - M.H. Rhodes, Inc.
    - RH-1, -2, -3, -4, -4A, 1953-1956 (Box 23)
    - RH-5, 1957 (Box 23)
    - RH-6, 1957 (Box 23)
    - RH-7, 1957-1958 (Box 23)
    - RH-8, -8A, 1957-1964 (Box 23)
    - RH-9
      - Billing, 1960-1961 (Box 23)
      - General Correspondence, 1960-1962 (Box 23)
      - Proposals and Reports, 1960-1961 (Box 23)
    - 1965 (Box 23)
    - Dial Designs, 1959 (Box 23)
  - Rhodes Timer (Box 23)
  - Ridge Tool Company, 1965-1968 (Box 23)
  - Robertshaw, 1959 (Box 23)
  - Rolled charts and drawings, See Rolled charts and drawings below, at end of Business files series.
  - Roper Corporation, 1968 (Box 23)
  - Rowe, 1952; 1968; 3 folders (Box 23)
  - Royal Metal
    - RM 101 Survey, 1959-1960 (Box 24)
    - Topeka Chair, 1959 (Box 24)
  - RSID
    - 1957-1965 (Box 24)
    - Design Responsibility (Box 24)
    - Logo, 1962 (Box 24)
    - Monogram (Box 24)
    - Office Information, 1963-1965 (Box 24)
    - Typesetting (Box 24)
  - RS
    - Agenda at H.C. Columbus, 1966-1967 (Box 24)
    - Letterhead (Box 24)
    - Talks
      - Sales Executive Club, 1957 (Box 24)
      - Scarsdale Rotary (Box 24)
  - Ryder, 1973; slide script; 2 folders (Box 24)
  - S-102, 1964 (Box 24)
  - Safe Flight
    - Marine Division (Box 24)
      - 1971 (Box 24)
      - Horn, 1971 (Box 24)
    - Miscellaneous, 1971 (Box 24)
  - Safes, 1958 (Box 24)
  - St. Regis Paper Company, 1945-1969 (Box 24)
  - SAM Talk, 1953; 1958; 2 folders (Box 24)
  - Samples, See Product models and samples below, at end of Business files series, and Metal samples, above.
  - Samples Showing Trademarks, 1961 (Box 24)
  - Sanborn Catalogue
  - Sanders (Box 24)
    - 1967, 2 folders (Box 24)
    - 601 (Box 24)
    - Miscellaneous, 1967 (Box 24)
  - Scale Talk, 1955 (Box 24)
  - Schaeffer Pen (Box 90)
  - Prof. Walter Schaer, 1964-1969 (Box 24)
  - F.A.O. Schwarz Catalogue (Box 24)
  - O.M. Scott and Sons Company, 1967-1969 (Box 24)
  - Sea Island (Box 24)
  - Seal, Inc., 1971-1972; 2 folders (Box 24)
  - Sears, 1974 (Box 24)
  - Security Regulations and Documents, 1962 (Box 24)
  - Security Steel Inc.
    - 1958 (Box 24)
    - Presentation, 1958 (Box 24)
    - Progress Reports, 1958 (Box 24)
  - Seeburg, 1964-1965; 1970; 2 folders (Box 24)
  - Servo Corporation, 1964; 1967; 3 folders (Box 24)
  - SF-2, 1971 (Box 24)
  - Sharp, 1970 (Box 24)
  - ShavAir of America, Inc. (Box 24)
  - W.A. Sheaffer Pen Company, 1968-1970; 3 folders (Box 24)
  - Simmons
    - Chairs, 1958; 2 folders (Box 25)
    - Display Rooms on NY Showfloor, 1934 (Box 25)
    - Dorm Line (Box 25)
    - Furniture Photos, 1933-1955 (Box 25)
    - Miscellaneous, 1967 (Box 25)
    - Miscellaneous/Dorm Line Sketches (Box 25)
    - Molded Plywood Chairs, 1957-1958 (Box 25)
    - Plastic Drawer Drawings, 1954 (Box 25)
    - Retouched Photos of 153 Line (Box 25)
    - Slides (Box 25)
    - Theme Line, 1953 (Box 25)
  - Slides (Box 25)
  - Slides, 7 boxes (Box 41)
  - Slides, 2 boxes, 1 bag (Box 42)
  - Slide Shows A, B, and C, 1958 (Box 25)
  - Society for Advancement of Management, 1952 (Box 25)
  - SOCONY Mobil Oil Company, 1962 (Box 25)
  - Sorensen and Company, 1962 (Box 25)
  - Speech (Box 25)
  - Speedry Chemical Products, Inc. (Box 25)
  - Raymond Spilman Talks, 1957-1963 (Box 25)
  - Staff College, 1967 (Box 25)
  - Staff Names Typesetting (Box 25)
  - Stanton Magnetics
    - 581-581EL, 1964 (Box 25)
    - 1969 (Box 25)
  - Steelcase (Box 25)
  - Steelcase, Inc.
    - 1966 (Box 25)
    - Miscellaneous, 1967 (Box 25)
  - Steno Books, 1965-1969; 2 folders (Box 90)
  - Studebaker Corporation Tractor Division, 1964 (Box 25)
  - Survey
    - Better Homes and Gardens, 1967 (Box 25)
    - The Camping Market, 1967 (Box 25)
    - The Cornell Kitchen, 1951; 2 folders (Box 25)
    - LIFE (Box 25)
  - T, 1967-1970 (Box 25)
  - Taft Pierce Exhibit, 1965 (Box 25)
  - Talk Notes, 1960 (Box 25)
  - Talks by Others, 1967-1969 (Box 25)
  - Technical Resume Mock-Up, 1963 (Box 26)
  - Technical Resumes, 2 folders (Box 26)
  - Telephone Call Record, 1960-1970 (Box 26)
  - TF-2, Bari, Italy, 1957
    - Graphics (Box 26)
    - Miscellaneous Drawings (Box 26)
  - TF-3, Lima, Peru, 1959 (Box 26)
  - Things To Do (Box 26)
  - Third International Trade Fair, 1963
    - Journal (Box 26)
    - Miscellaneous, 2 folders (Box 26)
  - Third Pacific International Trade Fair, 1963 (Box 26)
  - TK Foods (Box 26)
  - Tracerlab, Inc., 1961-1962 (Box 26)
  - Trade Fair, Lima, Peru
    - Billing, 1963-1964 (Box 26)
    - Contract, 1962-1963 (Box 26)
    - Proposal, 1962-1963 (Box 26)
  - Trans-Sonics, Inc., 1965; 2 folders (Box 26)
  - Truck Design (Box 26)
  - Turner Corporation, 1970 (Box 26)
  - Turner-Seymour Kitchen Tools (Box 26)
  - Underwood
    - 1959 (Box 26)
    - 125 Computer Model Study, 1958 (Box 26)
    - Manual Typewriter (Box 26)
    - Metal Cal Samples (Box 26)
    - Miscellaneous, 1958 (Box 26)
    - Miscellaneous Photographs (Box 26)
    - Underwood, Photos (Box 42)
    - Proportional Spacing, 1957 (Box 26)
    - Standard Portable Photographs (Box 26)
    - Stationery, 1958 (Box 26)
    - Typewriters and Trademarks (Box 26)
  - UNICEF Calendar, 1965 (Box 26)
  - Union Carbide, 1960-1964 (Box 27)
  - Uniroyal (Box 27)
  - United Shoe Machinery Company, 1966; 2 folders (Box 27)
  - University of Chicago, 1966-1967
    - Contract (Box 27)
    - Correspondence with Others (Box 27)
    - Material File (Box 27)
    - OCD Staff College (Box 27)
  - University of Kansas, 1962 (Box 27)
  - U.S. Army Natick Laboratories, 1966 (Box 27)
  - U.S. Gypsum
    - Miscellaneous, 1967-1968 (Box 27)
    - Slide Show (Box 27)
    - Textone Sales and Training Introduction, 1967; 3 folders (Box 27)
    - USG-1, 1967-1969 (Box 27)
  - USM
    - 1966-1967 (Box 27)
    - -2 and -3, 1966-1967 (Box 27)
    - Ammo, 1966 (Box 27)
    - Artwork, 1966 (Box 27)
    - Eyelet Machine, 1964-1966 (Box 27)
    - Graphics (Box 27)
    - Human Factors Study (Box 27)
    - Industrial Drawings, 1966 (Box 27)
    - Literature, 1961-1965; 4 folders (Box 27)
    - Miscellaneous, 1965 (Box 27)
    - Miscellaneous, 1966 (Box 28)
    - Product Case Histories, 1965-1966 (Box 28)
    - Tasks and Miscellaneous Input (Box 28)
  - Variplotter (Box 28)
  - VariTyper Corporation (Box 28)
  - Vinyl Samples (Box 28)
  - WA-1, 1967-1968 (Box 28)
  - WA-1A, 1968 (Box 28)
  - WA-2, 1967-1968 (Box 28)
  - Franz Wagner Color Samples (Box 28)
  - Wall Extendor Research Review (Box 28)
  - WAR-1, 1969 (Box 28)
  - Waring, 1969 (Box 28)
  - Washburn Company
    - Billing Folder, 1955-1959; 2 folders (Box 28)
    - Can Opener, 1956 (Box 28)
    - Cookie Lifter Blades (Box 28)
    - Correspondence, 1964 (Box 28)
    - Deluxe Chrome Plate Kitchen Ware Line, 1958-1959 (Box 28)
    - General, 1957-1959; 2 folders (Box 28)
    - General Correspondence, 1960-1964; 2 folders (Box 28)
    - Glass/Plastic, 1967-1968 (Box 28)
    - Grater, 1968 (Box 28)
    - Labels, 1955-1959 (Box 28)
    - Marketing Report, 1965 (Box 28)
    - Meeting Reports, 1962-1964 (Box 28)
    - Miscellaneous, 1963-1967; 2 folders (Box 28)
    - Miscellaneous Reprints, 1962 (Box 28)
    - Newspaper Clippings, 1965 (Box 28)
    - Personal, 1957-1959 (Box 28)
    - Presentation, 1967-1968 (Box 28)
    - Proposals
      - 1957-1959 (Box 28)
      - 1965 (Box 28)
      - New Kitchen Ware Graters, 1967 (Box 28)
    - Rockford (Box 28)
    - Stamford, Darien Meeting Reports, 1967-1969 (Box 28)
    - Study, 1965 (Box 28)
    - WA-6, 1954-1956 (Box 28)
    - WA-7, 1954-1955 (Box 28)
    - WA-8, 1955-1956 (Box 29)
    - WA-9, 1955-1957 (Box 29)
    - WA-10, 1956 (Box 29)
    - WA-11, 1955-1956 (Box 29)
    - WA-15a, -15b, -15c, 1956-1957 (Box 29)
    - WA-16, 1956-1959; 2 folders (Box 29)
    - WA-17, -18, -19, 1958 (Box 29)
    - WA-22
      - General Folder, 1959-1961 (Box 29)
      - Proposals and Reports, 1961 (Box 29)
    - WA-23, 1961
      - General Folder (Box 29)
      - Proposals and Reports (Box 29)
    - WA-24,1960 (Box 29)
    - WA-24, -25, 1961 (Box 29)
      - Rockford, 1967-1970 (Box 29)
      - Report, Final Pages, 1965 (Box 29)
      - Worcester, 1967 (Box 29)
  - Waterman Pen (Box 29)
  - Wearever
    - Briefs, 1967-1968 (Box 29)
    - Chillocothe, Ohio, 1966-1967 (Box 29)
    - Convenience Pre-Prepared Portion Controlled Institution Food, 1962-1969; 2 folders (Box 29)
    - Drawings (Box 29)
    - Future of Food and Food Preparation Products, 1967-1968 (Box 29)
    - Miscellaneous, 1968-1969; 5 folders (Box 29)
    - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1968 (Box 29)
    - New Product Ideas and Suggestions, 1968-1969 (Box 29)
    - Report, 1968; 4 folders (Box 29)
    - Reports, 1968; 2 folders (Box 30)
  - Witin Machine Works
    - 1964 (Box 30)
    - Program and Catalogues, 1964-1965 (Box 30)
  - Winchester, 1969-1970 (Box 30)
  - Worcester Advertising Club
    - RS Talk, 1957 (Box 30)
    - Speech, 1957 (Box 30)
  - Worcester Pressed Aluminum Corporation, 1965; 1967-1968; 3 folders (Box 30)
  - World's Fair Information, 1961 (Box 30)
  - WPAC-1, 1968 (Box 30)
  - Dave Wurster Clients, 1963 (Box 30)
  - Yankee Metal Products, 1968 (Box 30)
  - Art Work and Charts
    - Almar (Oversize 25)
    - Almar (Oversize 44)
    - Almar (Oversize 52)
    - AMSCO (Oversize 21)
    - AMSCO (Oversize 22)
    - AMSCO (Oversize 23)
    - AMSCO, logos (Oversize 27)
    - AMSCO, 2 items (Oversize 28)
    - AMSCO (Oversize 36)
    - AMSCO (Oversize 37)
    - AMSCO (Oversize 45)
    - AMSCO (Oversize 50)
    - Androck (Oversize 21)
    - Androck (Oversize 25)
    - Androck (Oversize 34)
    - Androck (Oversize 35)
    - Androck (Oversize 47)
    - Androck (Oversize 50)
    - Art Metal (Oversize 21)
    - Art Metal (Oversize 38)
    - Astatic (Oversize 23)
    - Astatic (Oversize 29)
    - Astatic (Oversize 45)
    - Bari Trade Fair (Oversize 25)
    - Better Built (Oversize 50)
    - Bozak (Oversize 38)
    - Bozak (Oversize 39)
    - Bozak (Oversize 48)
    - Brochure Pages Artwork (Oversize 24)
    - Canadian Johns Manville (Oversize 25)
    - Char Broil (Oversize 25)
    - Char Broil (Oversize 28)
    - Char Broil (Oversize 37)
    - Char Broil (Oversize 45)
    - Civil Defense (Oversize 25)
    - Civil Defense (Oversize 31)
    - CO-4 (Oversize 42)
    - Color Aid (Oversize 47)
    - Columbus Iron Works (Oversize 44)
    - Columbus Iron Works (Oversize 45)
    - Cosco (Oversize 22)
    - Cosco (Oversize 23)
    - Cosco (Oversize 30)
    - Cosco (Oversize 31)
    - Cosco (Oversize 39)
    - CR-2 (Oversize 28)
    - DCB-1 (Oversize 31)
    - Dexter Folding Machine (Oversize 25)
    - Dow-Spilman Report (Oversize 25)
    - General Foods (Oversize 50)
    - General Thrift Corporation (Oversize 36)
    - GTC (Oversize 23)
    - Halliwell (Oversize 34)
    - Halliwell (Oversize 46)
    - Halliwell (Oversize 47)
    - Halliwell, 2 items (Oversize 29)
    - IBM (Oversize 22)
    - ID Slide Show (Oversize 33)
    - Ideal Toys (Oversize 50)
    - Industrial Design Show (Oversize 25)
    - J.C. Penney (Oversize 37)
    - Lima Trade Fair (Oversize 50)
    - Lima, Peru Exhibit Graphic Ideas (Oversize 41)
    - M.H. Rhodes (Oversize 45)
    - M.H. Rhodes (Oversize 47)
    - Mack Trucks (Oversize 21)
    - Maxwell House (Oversize 20)
    - Maxwell House (Oversize 26)
    - Monmouth Heights (Oversize 25)
    - MRD-20-60 (Oversize 31)
    - Nortype (Oversize 29)
    - Photostat, 2 items (Oversize 41)
    - Pickering (Oversize 28)
    - Planned Design Charts (Oversize 33)
    - Postage Meter (Oversize 36)
    - Preliminary Letterheads (Oversize 23)
    - Project Procedure Chart (Oversize 28)
    - Radiation Inc. (Oversize 23)
    - Randall (Oversize 29)
    - RH-9 (Oversize 31)
    - RS Brochure (Oversize 52)
    - RS Brochure Pages (Oversize 22)
    - RS Brochure Pages (Oversize 51)
    - RS Brochure Typography (Oversize 46)
    - RS Business Card (Oversize 50)
    - RS Design Services (Oversize 23)
    - RS Promotion Photos (Oversize 49)
    - RS Proposal Charts (Oversize 40)
    - Safe Flight (Oversize 34)
    - Seal (Oversize 35)
    - Sharp, 2 items (Oversize 44)
    - Shavair (Oversize 33)
    - Sherr and McDermott (Oversize 22)
    - Simmons (Oversize 35)
    - Simmons (Oversize 43)
    - Spilman House (Oversize 25)
    - Staff College (Oversize 22)
    - Staff College (Oversize 31)
    - TK Foods (Oversize 41)
    - TK Foods (Oversize 50)
    - TK Foods, 8 items (Oversize 32)
    - U.S.Gypsum, 2 items (Oversize 36)
    - Underwood (Oversize 25)
    - Underwood (Oversize 38)
    - Underwood (Oversize 43)
    - Underwood (Oversize 48)
    - Underwood, 2 items (Oversize 52)
    - Variplotter (Oversize 25)
    - Vend Mag. Illustrations (Oversize 23)
    - Waring (Oversize 52)
    - Washburn, 2 items (Oversize 23)
    - Miscellaneous (Oversize 25)
    - Miscellaneous, 2 items (Oversize 32)
    - Miscellaneous (Oversize 41)
    - Miscellaneous (Oversize 43)
    - Miscellaneous (Oversize 44)
    - Miscellaneous (Oversize 47)
  - Finished products
    - Cosco Baby Crib (Box 87)
    - Cosco Infant Bed (Box 89)
    - Cosco Tubing (Box 88)
  - Product Models and Samples
    - Almar (Box 43)
    - AMSCO (Box 48)
    - AMSCO (Box 78)
    - AMSCO (Oversize 54)
    - Androck (Box 44)
    - Androck (Box 45)
    - Androck (Box 46)
    - Androck (Box 47)
    - Androck (Box 48)
    - Androck (Box 77)
    - Androck (Box 78)
    - Androck (Box 81)
    - Androck (Box 91)
    - Astatic (Box 49)
    - B.T. Crump (Box 83)
    - Bozak (Box 48)
    - Byc. Hardware Baskets (Box 75)
    - Canadian Johns Manville (Oversize 53)
    - Ceiling Tiles (Box 50)
    - Chair Models (Box 76)
    - Chair Models (Oversize Crate 1)
    - Charter (Box 83)
    - Cosco (Box 51)
    - Cosco (Box 52)
    - Cosco (Box 79)
    - Cosco (Box 83)
    - Cosco (Oversize 53)
    - Cosco (Oversize 54)
    - Filbrook (Box 53)
    - Filbrook (Box 54)
    - Glaiser-Steers (Box 54)
    - Glassware Samples (Box 65)
    - Lamp Shade (Box 85)
    - Lear-Siegler (Box 80)
    - Maxwell House (Box 55)
    - Maxwell House (Box 56)
    - Maxwell House (Box 57)
    - Maxwell House (Box 58)
    - Maxwell House (Box 59)
    - Maxwell House (Box 60)
    - Maxwell House (Box 61)
    - Maxwell House (Box 62)
    - PADCO (Box 54)
    - Pickering (Box 66)
    - Primus (Box 54)
    - Primus (Box 67)
    - Randall (Box 80)
    - Sanders (Box 82)
    - Sketches (Box 68)
    - Soundscriber (Box 69)
    - Soundscriber (Box 70)
    - Soundscriber (Box 71)
    - Stereo Turntable (Box 83)
    - Table Lamp (Box 78)
    - TK Foods (Box 72)
    - TK Foods (Box 73)
    - TK Foods (Box 74)
    - TK Foods (Box 75)
    - Underwood (Box 48)
    - Underwood (Box 78)
    - Underwood (Box 84)
    - Washburn Hand Tools (Box 75)
    - Washburn (Oversize 53)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 63)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 64)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 65)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 77)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 85)
    - Miscellaneous (Oversize 54)
    - Miscellaneous (Oversize 55)
  - Rolled Charts and Drawings
    - AMSCO (Oversize 6)
    - AMSCO (Oversize 11)
    - AMSCO (Oversize 12)
    - AMSCO (Oversize 16)
    - Androck (Box 86)
    - Androck (Oversize 13)
    - Androck (Oversize 14)
    - Androck (Oversize 16)
    - Androck (Oversize 18)
    - Art Metal, 2 items (Box 86)
    - Art Metal (Oversize 5)
    - Astatic (Box 86)
    - Astatic (Oversize 5)
    - B.T. Crump (Oversize 3)
    - Bari Trade Fair (Box 86)
    - Better Built (Box 86)
    - Better Built (Oversize 9)
    - Better Built (Oversize 18)
    - Bozak, 2 items (Box 86)
    - Bozak (Oversize 15)
    - Char Broil, 2 items (Oversize 8)
    - Civil Defense (Oversize 6)
    - Cober (Box 86)
    - Columbus Iron Works (Oversize 2)
    - Columbus Iron Works (Oversize 8)